人鬼情未了
哦 太棒了！
Oh, but this is great.
-哇！ -太不可思议了
- Wow! - Oh, That's incredible.
上层至少有七八英尺高
There's gotta be at least seven or eight feet up there.
还有积了八十年的灰尘
And 80 years of dust.
看看这么高
Look at all this height.
我们可以把睡房建在楼上 下层就有这么大的空间了
We could put our bedroom upstairs, and that will leave us with all this space.
-有什么用？ -空间大就好
- For what? - Just space.
一 二 三！
One, two, three!
-四？ -来吧！
- And four? - Come on.
四！
Four.
五！
And five.
小心…小心这个！
Watch... watch this.
天啊！这地方真大
God, this place is huge.
-真棒 -天啊
-It's beautiful. -God!
-这房子真是棒极了 -不可思议
- You guys, it's absolutely incredible. - Incredible.
粉饰一下就可以了
A little paint.
我看你们明天就能 以双倍的价钱把它卖出去
I'd say you could sell this tomorrow and double your money.
-卡尔 你真是财迷心窍 -一点点吧
- Carl, you're obsessed. - A little bit.
哇 快看啊
Whoa, look.
嘿 这是一枚1898年的 带印第安人头像的硬币
Hey, it's an Indian-head penny. 1898.
-这是好运的预兆 -你就是好运的预兆
- It's a good omen. - You're the good omen.
哦 好极了！
Oh, it's so great.
我让露丝将你和鲍勃卡汗 开会时间从三点改到四点了
I had Rose move your 3:00 with Bob kahan to 4:00,
因为嘉里亚伦 昨晚打来电话
'cause Gary Alan called at the end of the day yesterday
说他必须跟你见面商量 阁楼粉饰的最终出价
and said he has to see you about the final painting bids for the loft.
他只在可以三点见面 可以吗？
3:00 is the only time he could make it. Is that okay?
森姆？
Sam?
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
老兄 放松点 噢 对不起
- Would you relax, man? - Oh, I'm sorry.
你又不是要去做脑手术
This is not brain surgery you're going into.
跟这些日本人推销 让我特别紧张
Pitching these Japanese guys makes me so nervous.
森姆 你会做得好好的 放松点 好吗？
Sam, you're going to be great. Okay?
我的问题是 我该说些什么？
I mean, what am I supposed to say?
我又不能给他们讲 瑞典啦啦队女孩的笑话
I mean, I can't very well tell them my Swedish pom-pom girl joke, you know.
这衣服真不错啊 你在哪儿买的？
Those are great. Where'd you get those?
挺好吧？莫莉买的 你觉得怎么样？适合我吗？
Nice, huh? Molly. What do you think? Are they me?
哇 快看 法拉利红头车
Oh, man, look at that. A testarossa.
我看你还是先将你那辆 福特野马的贷款付清吧
I think you ought to pay off your mustang first.
你感觉怎么样？ 医生怎么说？
How you feeling? What'd the doctor say?
他说是传染病 这病真的…
He said that it was contagious. That it was really...
不会吧 是真的
No. Yeah.
他说我今天不应该上班
He said that I shouldn't even be coming in today.
-疹子怎么样了？ -疹子？
- What about the rash? - The rash?
疹子也非常容易传染
The rash is also incredibly contagious.
-他说这两种病都在扩散 -噢 太糟了
- He said they've both been spreading. - No.
-又在你的生殖器出现了？ -是 是啊 就在那里
- On your genitals again? - Yeah, yeah. Right on the genitals.
基本上全身都是 他说我不应该接触任何人
Basically everywhere. He said that I shouldn't touch anyone.
不好意思 我很抱歉
Excuse me. I'm sorry.
-你这个变态的家伙 -我知道
- You're sick. - I know.
-早晨 保罗 -早晨 卡尔森姆
- Good morning, Paul. - Good morning, Carl. Sam.
嘿 保罗
Hey, Paul.
-早晨 维特先生 -早晨 苏珊 你气色真好
- Morning, Mr. wheat. - Morning, Susan. You are looking good.
-森姆 -噢 对 对 在我这
- Sam. - Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
-给你 -谢谢
- Here it is. - Thanks.
-早晨 森姆 -早晨 露丝
- Good morning, Sam. - Good morning, Rose.
-听着 那些日本人什么时候… -他们已经到了
- Oh, listen, the kobiashi people... - They're already here.
-他们提早到了 -我知道
- They're early. - I know.
-过来一下 -噢 安迪狄伦来过电话……
- Come here. - Oh, and Andy Dillon called...
-他们来了多久 -大约十分钟吧
- How long have they been here? - About 10 minutes.
安迪狄伦打过电话说他需要 十点前转九十万到奥尔巴尼
Andy Dillon called and he says he needs $900,000 transferred to Albany by 10:00.
-十点之前？ -对
- By 10:00? - Yes.
失陪一阵
Excuse me.
-卡尔？ -什么事？
- Carl? - Yeah?
-早晨 -卡尔
- Good morning. - Carl.
比尔 稍等一下
Bill, hang on one second.
狄伦需要十点前 转九十万到奥尔巴尼
Dillon needs $900,000 in Albany by 10:00.
你能把钱转到 他的出粮户口上吗？
Can you transfer it to his payroll account?
-得 但要用你的迁转授权密码 -好的
- Yeah, I'm gonna need your Mac code. - Okay.
-小心点 好吧？ -明白
- Discretion, right? - Got it.
-放心 我立刻就去办 -好的 谢谢
- You bet. I'll do it right now. - Okay, thanks.
比尔 我稍后再打给你 好的
Yeah. Bill, I'm going to call you back. Okay.
好 好 可以了 好 很好
Okay, okay, that's fine. It's fine. It's fine!
老兄 离得太远了
Man, it's too far out.
你能明白吗 老兄？
Can you get this, man?
你们是哪里来的？ 纽约芭蕾舞团吗？
Where are you guys from, the New York City ballet?
差一点就够到了
Almost.
-救了你一命 -你这个衰人吓死我了
- Saved your life. - You shit. You scared me to death.
你为什么吓我？
Why did you do that?
总比看见你这美人 粉身碎骨的好
It's better than seeing this gorgeous body splattered all over the place.
小心点 让开一下
Look out. Look out.
抓住了
Grab it.
-森姆？莫 你们在家吗？ -系卡尔 你叫他来的？
- Sam, mol, are you guys home? - That's Carl. Did you invite him?
-免费劳工 -卡尔
- Slave labor. - Carl.
-做什么？ -快些 来帮忙
- What? - Hurry, help.
噢 我的天啊
Oh, my god.
抬下面 好了
- Near the bottom. - L1 got it.
现在把它放下 对
- Now go down. What? Just down here? - Yeah.
-放这里是吧？ -小心你的脚趾
- Just right here? - Watch your toes.
好了
I got it.
-嘿 你们想把这个放在哪里？ -在睡房
- Hey, where do you want this? - In the bedroom.
好样的
Good girl.
-天啊 这地方看起来真好 -是啊
- God, this place looks great. - Yeah.
你喜欢啊？ 喜欢？何止是喜欢
- You like it, huh? - Like? Like is hardly the word.
我没想到这里会变这么漂亮 真不可思议
I had no idea it'd be this beautiful. It's incredible.
莫莉 这个放哪里？
Molly, what about her?
我们就暂时把她放在那吧 等其他东西进来之后
Well, why don't we just leave her there until we get the other stuff in?
这些是什么？
We can figure out... “What are these?
噢 我来给你看看
Oh, let me show you.
-帮我把这个揭起来好吗？ -是这儿吗？
- Hey, you wanna help me lift this up? - What, here? - Yeah.
哇
Wow.
-我刚整好的 你觉得怎么样？ -太棒了 我很喜欢
- I just finished it. What do you think? - It's fantastic. I love it.
森姆 这张椅子 放在这里干嘛？
Sam, what's this chair doing here?
-什么意思？我喜欢这张椅子 -我知道你喜欢
- What do you mean? I love that chair. - I know you love this chair.
-但我们不是说过… -是 可是它一直陪伴我的
- But we discussed this and... - Yeah, I've had it forever.
我是说看电视的时候 我可以坐这张椅子
I mean just, when I watch TV, I sit in it.
-亲爱的 这张椅子太难看了 -那又怎样？
- Baby, this chair is ugly. - So?
-它与其他东西都不相配 -它跟我就很相配
- And it doesn't go with anything. - It goes with me.
你说对了 跟你太配了
You're right. It does.
-我们得把它粉饰一下 -什么？
- We'll paint it. - We'll what?
-你还好吗？ -我没事
- You okay? - I'm fine.
-怎么了？ -没什么
- What's the matter? - Nothing.
你在担心升职的事？
Are you worried about the promotion?
不 也不是
No, not really.
-那是什么？是因为我们同住？ -不是
- Then what? Is it moving in together? - No.
我也不知道 是生活中的很多事情
I don't know. It's a lot of things.
我只是不想让好梦成空
I just don't want the bubble to burst.
就好像…
It seems like
我的生活中 一旦有好的事情出现
whenever anything good in my life happens,
我就会担心失去它
I'm just afraid I'm going to lose it.
我爱你 我真的很爱你
I love you. I really love you.
我都系
Ditto.
飞行员的第一份故障报告称
The pilot's first report of trouble was that
飞机尾部的二号引擎发生爆炸
he blew the number two engine, the one in the tail of the plane.
机上载满了乘客
It was fully loaded.
天啊 又一起空难
Oh, Jesus, another one.
唉 不要看了
Oh, don't watch that.
我该取消去洛杉矶的旅行 这种事情总是接二连三的
I should cancel my la trip. These things always happen in threes.
森姆 不要乱讲了 你一向都是吉人天相的
Sam, get serious. Besides, you lead a charmed life.
是啊 他们以前不也是嘛
Oh, yeah. So did they.
真难以置信 就那样 眼前一黑 生命就完结了
It's amazing, just like that. Blackout.
♪ My love
♪ My darling
♪ I've hungered for...
-你在干什么？ -我睡不着
- What are you doing? - I couldn't sleep.
天啊 我肯定是昏睡过去了
Boy, I really must have passed out.
-现在几点了？ -凌晨两点
- What time is it? - It's 2:00 A.M.
♪ Goes by
♪ So slowly
♪ Any time
♪ Can do so much
♪ Are you
♪ Still mine
哦 完了 我希望这不是你的杰作
Oh, no. I hope it wasn't a masterpiece.
现在肯定不是了
Well, it's not now.
-我能帮忙吗？ -当然
- Can I help? - Yeah.
把你的手放在这儿 将手弄湿
Put your hands up here. Get them wet.
让粘土在你的指间滑过
Now, just let the Clay slide between your fingers.
♪ God speed your love
♪ To me
♪ Lonely rivers Flow
♪ To the sea
♪ To the open arms
♪ Of the sea
♪ Yeah
♪ Lonely rivers sigh
♪ Wait for me
♪ I'll be coming home
♪ Oh
♪ My love
♪ My darling
♪ I've hungered
♪ Hungered for your touch
♪ A long
♪ Lonely time
♪ And time
♪ Goes by
♪ So slowly
♪ Any time
♪ Can do so much
♪ Are you
♪ Still mine
♪ I need
♪ Your love
♪ I
♪ I need your love
♪ God speed your love
♪ To me
（输入转移授权密码： XXXXX-X）
（联合现金账户 11 853 090.88美元）
噢 不是吧
Oh, no.
怎么了？
What's the matter?
出了故障 有事吗？
A glitch. What's up?
我入不到马克格林伯格 还有拉瑞怀特的帐户
The Mark Greenberg and Larry white accounts.
转移授权密码用不到
I can't get in. The Mac code doesn't work.
-不 是我把它改了 -你改了？为什么？
- No, I changed it. - You changed it? Why?
没有什么只是想调查一下
Nothing. I just want to nose around a bit.
有什么问题吗？
Is something wrong?
你可以保守秘密吗？
Can you keep a secret?
当然 可以啊
Yeah, sure.
怎么了？
What's up?
这些户口里面的钱太多了
There's too much money in these accounts.
钱太多了？ 这不可能 怎么会有…
Too much money? That's impossible. How could there be...
C72273
C72273.
森姆 这个花你好几个小时 等我来做吧
Sam, this is going to take you hours. Let me do this.
已经花了我好几个小时了
It already has taken me hours.
那就让我拿回去帮你查清楚
Well, let me take it back and figure it out for you.
不 不 没事 我要跟它战斗到底
No, no, that's okay. It's... it's like a vendetta now.
-不过还是要谢谢你 我很感激 -那好吧
- Thanks, though. I appreciate it. - Okay.
-如果感觉眼睛累就叫我 -好的
- If you start to go blind, just shout. - Okay.
我刚才正要问你 今晚你和莫莉做什么？
Listen, I was wondering, what are you and mol doing tonight?
我们去剧院 她要去看「马克白」
We're going to the theater. She wants to see MacBeth.
我个人认为她喜欢看 穿紧身衣的男人 你去吗？
I think she likes the guys in tights, personally. You want to go?
不 谢了 你回来全部讲给我听吧
No, thanks. I want a full report, though.
一阵见 好
Later. Yeah.
真好看
Wonderful.
棒极了 太好看了
Excellent. Great.
-我喜欢这部剧 -是啊
- Well, I loved it. - Yes.
-我看都入迷了 -我发现了
- I was spellbound the whole time. - I could tell.
其余观众在你回响的鼾声中 也发现了这一点
And so could the rest of the audience with that resonating snore of yours.
我跟你讲过梅丽莎说的话吗？
Did I tell you what Melissa said?
-嗯 说了差不多六次了 -才没有呢
- Yeah, about six times. - It wasn't six times.
-别这么不耐烦嘛 -好吧
- Now quit being so blasé about this. - Okay.
这真的很重要我有两件作品 快要在她的画廊展出了
Now, this is really important. I'm gonna have two pieces in her gallery.
《纽约时报》经常评论 这家画廊
The New York times reviews her gallery all the time.
莫莉  《纽约时报》的人 不过是一些灰心丧气
Molly, the New York times is just some frustrated little critic
立心不良 考艺校又不及格的评论家
with pimples on his ass who flunked out of art school.
所以谁会在乎他们的看法呢
So who cares what they think?
八百万的读者会在乎
About eight million readers, that's who.
才不是 这些读者只看体育版
Nah, they're just reading the sports page.
你的作品真的很美
Your work is really beautiful.
-真的 -谢谢
- It really is. - Thanks.
其他人的看法并不重要 我的看法才重要
And it shouldn't matter what anyone else thinks. Just what I think.
我要嫁给你 森姆
I want to marry you, Sam.
什么？你说什么？
What? What?
没错
Yep.
我一直在想这件事
I've been thinking about it.
想了很多 我觉得我们索性结婚吧
I've been thinking about it a lot, and I think we should just do it.
-你是认真的 -是的
- You're serious. - Yeah.
你怎么这副表情？
What's that look for?
你向来都不愿意谈论这件事
You never wanted to talk about it.
-你爱我吗 森姆？ -你觉得呢？
- Do you love me, Sam? - Now, what do you think?
-那你为什么从来都不说呢？ -你这话什么意思？
- Why don't you ever say it? - What do you mean, why don't I ever say it?
-我总说啊 我感觉就像… -不 你没说过
- I say it all the time. I feel like... - No, you don't.
你说的是 「我都系」 那是不一样的
You say, "ditto," and that's not the same.
人们总是说[我爱你] 但其实毫无意义
People say "I love you" all the time, and it doesn't mean anything.
你知道吗 人有时候需要听到这句话
You know, sometimes you need to hear it.
我需要听你说这句话
I need to hear it.
我们走吧
Let's go.
-我们该怎么办？ -我来应付
- What should we do? - Let me handle it.
-你想要什么？ -糟糕
- What do you want? - Shit.
你的钱包 快给我！
Your wallet. Give it to me!
森姆 快给他吧
Sam, just give it to him.
可以 把钱拿走好了 给我们留下…
Okay. Just take the money. Just leave us...
不 不要 森姆！
No, no, Sam!
你这混蛋！
You son of a bitch!
森姆！别打了
Sam, no!
来人救命啊！
Somebody help us!
天啊！森姆！
Jesus Christ! Sam!
快停手！
Just get off!
来人 快来人救救我们！
Somebody! Somebody help us!
森姆 你就…
Sam, just let...
森姆 停手！别打了森姆！
Sam, just stop it! Stop it, Sam!
莫莉？
Molly?
莫莉？他有…
Molly? He got...
哦 亲爱的 坚持住
Oh, baby, hold on.
你会没事的
You're gonna be okay.
来人 来人啊！ 来人救救我们啊！
Somebody! Somebody! Somebody help us!
森姆 噢 我的天啊
Sam. Oh, my god.
森姆 坚持住 亲爱的
Oh, Sam, come on. Hold on, baby.
马上就有人来了 你会没事的
Someone's gonna come. We're gonna be okay.
来人啊！快来人救救我们啊！
Somebody! Somebody help me!
快来人啊！
Please, anybody.
帮帮我 请你们帮帮我！
Help me, please, help me.
没事了 负姐 冷静点 好吗？
It's okay, lady. Take it easy, all right?
哦 天啊！
Oh, god!
我们会帮你的
We'll help you, okay?
莫莉？莫莉？莫莉？
Molly? Molly? Molly?
莫莉
Molly.
我们该怎么办？ 我们该怎么办？
What should we do? What should we do?
怎么了？怎么回事？怎么…
What? What's happening? What's...
他还有呼吸吗？
Is he breathing?
我不知道他还有没有呼吸
Is he breathing? I don't know if he's breathing.
哦 天啊 森姆 坚持住 坚持住 亲爱的 坚持住
Oh, god, Sam, hold on. Hold on, baby. Hold on.
哦 天啊
Oh, my god.
快啊！老兄
Come on, man.
没事的 快啊 会没事的
All right. Okay, come on, it's all right.
开始吧
Here we go.
好了 你按这边一二…
All right, there you go. One, two...
森姆 别离开我！森姆坚持住！
Sam, don't you leave me! Sam, hold on!
森姆！
Sam!
哦 森姆！
Oh, Sam!
（急救室）
Emergency room.
好的 马上到
All right. Right away.
简森小姐 请到这边
Miss Jensen, if you'll step this way, please.
心脏科 请转接255号分机
Cardiology, please dial extension 255...
-你怎么了？ -什么？
- So, what happened to you? - “What?
你是新来的吧？ 我看得出来
You're new, huh? I can tell.
-你在跟我说话吗？ -嘿 别紧张
- Are you talking to me? - Hey, relax.
你知道吗 现在跟从前不同了 一切都不同了
It ain't like before, you know. It's a whole new ball of wax.
-你是谁？ -我在等我妻子
- Who are you? - Oh, I'm waiting for my wife.
她在心脏科的4C病房 正努力战胜病魔呢
She's in 4c, cardiac wing. She's fighting it.
中枪了？中枪的基本都会死
Shot, huh? That'll do it every time.
可怜的家伙 嘿 你慢慢就适应了
Poor bastard. Hey, you may as well get used to it.
你可能要在这里等好耐
You could be here for a long while.
过来 我讲一个秘密你知
Come here, I'll tell you a secret.
门不像你想像的那么差 嗖一下就过去 根本挡不住你
Doors ain't as bad as you think. Zip, zap, they ain't nothing at all.
你会明白的 慢慢就识
You'll see. You'll catch on.
这位病人发生纤维性颤动
This patient's fibrillating.
电击板在哪里？快拿来
Where's the paddles? Get them up here.
他不行了
He ain't gonna make it.
这种情况我见过无数次了 他要去了
I've seen it a million times. He's a goner.
-他还在颤动 -请闪开
- He's still fibrillating. - Clear.
请闪开
Clear.
看见了吗？天使来了
You see? Here they come.
幸运的家伙
Lucky bastard.
来的也可能是地狱的鬼魂 你是猜不到的
It could have been the other ones. You never know.
谁是…
Who are...
护士长 请转接线生
Nursing supervisor, dial the operator, please.
护士长 请转接线生员
Nursing supervisor, dial the operator.
不！
No!
救救我！
Help me.
哦 上帝啊！救救我
Oh, god, help me.
我陷入沼泽的深渊 无处可立足
"Li am sunk in the abysmal swamp where there is no foothold.
我陷入深深的水底
"I have reached the watery depths.
洪水将我淹没
"The flood overwhelms me.
我呼喊至声嘶力竭
"I am wearied with calling."
在与我们的朋友 森姆维特永别之际
As we say farewell to our friend Sam wheat,
让我们铭记他的善良
we are reminded of his kindness,
他的慷慨 他乐观向上的精神
his generosity, his buoyancy of spirit.
以及我们所珍惜的一切 我们心爱的人
All that we treasure, our loved ones,
我们的挚友 我们的身体
our friends, our body,
我们的心灵
our mind,
都不属于我们
are but on loan to us.
我们必须将一切都归还上苍
We must surrender them all.
我们是同路的过客 最终走向同样的终点
We are all travelers on the same road which leads to the same end.
我们心爱的人 即已拥有了永恒的生命
As our loved one enters eternal life,
就让我们铭记爱亦永恒
let us remember that love too is eternal.
虽然我们仍将怀念他
That although we will miss him,
但我们的爱将照亮宇宙 驱走黑暗
our love will light the void and dispel the darkness.
我今天去取你的恤衫了
I picked up your shirts today.
我不知道为什么
I don't know why.
雷诺兹先生让我代他问候你
Mr. Reynolds told me to tell you hello.
我忍不住大哭了起来
I broke into tears.
我好像每分钟都在想你
It's like I think about you every minute.
似乎还能感觉到你的存在
It's like I can still feel you.
我在这里 莫
I'm here, mol.
佛洛依德 怎么了 小猫咪？ 怎么了？
Floyd, what's the matter, kitty? What's the matter?
你这只疯猫
Crazy cat.
森姆？
Sam?
我真是傻了
That's really stupid.
-我喜欢这张照片 -很棒
- I love this picture. - It's great.
办公室用品
Office.
哦 让我看一下这个 这是…
Oh, let me see that. It's...
-森姆的电话簿 -对
- Sam's address book. - Right.
大卫布鲁贝克88年新港音乐会
Dave brubeck, Newport, '88.
-这个我该弃掉吗？ -别掉
- Should I toss them? - No.
为什么不弃掉？莫莉 我们讨厌那场音乐会
No? Molly, we hated that concert.
嘿
Hey.
-这些你都要留下？ -胃药你也留着？
- Oh, you wanted to save those? - Rolaids?
莫莉 你在做什么？
Molly, what are you doing?
我只是太挂住他了 卡尔
I just miss him, Carl.
我也是
Me, too.
（森姆的办公用品）
（办公用品）
-卡尔？ -什么事？
- Carl? - Yeah?
稍等一下 等等
Wait a minute. Wait.
-什么？ -那个盒子不弃掉
- What? - Not that one.
哪个？噢 真对不起
Which? Oh, I'm sorry.
-我不是有意要拿走的 -没关系
- I didn't mean to put that on there. - That's okay.
嘿 莫莉 你不妨也出去走走 外面已经是夏天了
Hey, Molly, why don't you come? It's like summer outside.
不 真的不必了 我…我无这个心情
No, I really don't. I... I'm not up for it.
来吧 莫 出去走走吧
Come on, mol, just for a walk.
-出去走走对你有好处 -我不想去
- It'd be good for you to get out. - I don't want to.
莫莉 你不能整天都呆在这里
Molly, you can't stay in here all day.
-这对你的身体不好 -不 卡尔 我做不到！
- It's not healthy for you. - Look, Carl, I can't do it!
莫莉 死的人不是你
Molly, you're not the one who died.
-对不起 -你不必道歉
- I'm sorry. - Don't apologize.
该死
Shit.
也许你是对的
Maybe you're right.
-就走一小会儿吧 -这才是好姑娘
- Maybe just a short one. - Attagirl.
-我很抱歉 -没事了
- I'm sorry. - Don't worry about it.
莫莉？
Molly?
你来这里做干什么？
What are you doing here?
你这个王八蛋！
You bastard.
混蛋！
You son of a bitch!
你要干什么？
What do you want?
莫莉？
Molly?
莫莉 快出去！
Molly, get out!
天啊
Oh, my god.
不 莫莉 别进去 求求你 千万别进去
No, Molly. No, Molly, no, no. Please, no.
莫莉 莫莉 他有枪 莫莉！
Molly, Molly, he's got a gun. Molly!
嗨 小猫咪 你好啊
Hi, kitty. Hi.
你要是敢伤害她 我就杀了…
You hurt her, I'll kill...
莫莉
Molly.
该死
Shit.
有人吗？谁呀？
Is somebody there? Hello?
谁？
Hello?
你干什么？
What are you doing?
快放手！你要干什么？
Let go! What are you doing?
不
No!
你喜欢火车吗？
Like trains?
滚出去！这是我的地盘！
Stay out! This is mine!
他妈的
Shit.
是我 东西我没拿到 她回家了
It's me. I couldn't get it. She came home.
给我几天时间 老兄 我会再去的
In a couple of days, man. I'll go back.
放松一点 我会拿到手的
Relax. I'll get it.
你要拿什么？
Get what?
你是谁？ 你想从我们这里拿什么？
Who are you? What do you want from us?
不 你远离她一点
No. You stay away from her.
你听见了没有？
Do you hear me?
不准你接近她！
You stay away from her!
（阿徹及&阿徹律师事务所）
（灵媒）
（只需二十美元 就能与已故者交流）
罗莎圣地牙哥？
Rosa Santiago?
请坐
Please be seated.
灵媒大师马上就来
Our sister will be with us soon.
奥德梅大师 请恩赐我们一睹您的真容吧
Sister oda Mae, Grant us the gift of your all-seeing presence.
请现在就现身吧
Appear before us now.
圣地牙哥夫人？
Mrs. Santiago?
我是奥德梅布朗
I'm oda Mae brown.
我知道你想与你的先生通话
I understand you wish to contact your husband.
我相信他今天会出现的
I believe he'll be with us today.
哦 谢谢 谢谢你
Oh, thank you. Thank you.
但你知道吗 圣地牙哥夫人…
But you know, Mrs. Santiago,
另一个世界深不可测
there's no telling about that other world.
你必须是虔诚的信徒才行 圣地牙哥夫人
So you've got to be a believer, Mrs. Santiago.
你是虔诚的信徒吗？
Are you a believer?
我相信 我相信
Si si I believe. I believe.
那么我们开始吧
Then let us begin.
不行 我做不到  这太困难了
I can't. I can't. It's too difficult.
看来我无法与他取得联系 我…感受不到他的…等等！
I just can't seem to make contact. I... I don't feel his... no, wait!
我有点感觉了
I'm feeling something.
他认识一个叫安娜的人吗？
Did he know someone by the name of Anna?
康斯维罗？露西塔？朱莉安塔？
Consuelo? Lucita? Julietta?
约瑟芬娜？琳达？玛利亚？
Josephina? Linda? Maria?
他母亲的名字是玛利亚
Si, si. His mama. She is Maria.
好极了 感谢上帝！ 我就知道他和母亲在一起
Yes. Praise god! I knew he was with his mama.
哦 天啊
Oh, my god.
这太难了 他们有两个人 我不肯定我可不可以
It's too difficult. It's two of them. I'm not sure I can do that.
-这太费力了…这… -我可以加钱
- It's so trying... it's... - Oh, I pay more.
-加多少？加多少？ -二十美元
- How much? How much? - $20.
哦 真有你的办法 要榨干她的每分钱啊
Oh, way to go. Milk her for every penny.
好的 我们可以重新开始了
Yes, I believe we can start again.
感谢上帝 感谢耶稣
Praise the lord. Thank you, Jesus.
欢迎你 圣地牙哥夫人
Welcome, Mrs. Santiago.
你今天真好彩 鬼门关大开
You're fortunate today. The spirits are churning.
我老公来了？ 感谢仁慈的上帝！
- My husband? - Have mercy!
哦 真的？在哪里？
Oh, yeah? Where?
朱里奥？ 是的
Julio? Yes.
我感觉到他的气息了
I feel his vibration.
我看到他了！
I see him!
他好吗？他看上去怎样？
How is he? How does he look?
哦 他真是个英俊的男人
Oh, he's a handsome man.
英俊？
Handsome?
圣地牙哥夫人 天父国度里的所有人都很英俊
Mrs. Santiago, in our father's kingdom, we're all handsome.
哦 朱里奥
Oh, Julio.
朱里奥朝我们走过来了 我看到他了！
Julio's coming towards us. I see him!
他来了！他就在那里！
He's coming! He's there!
他穿着一身黑色的西装
He's dressed in a black suit.
黑色西装？
Black suit?
也可能是蓝色的
Could be blue.
简直是胡说八道
What a crock of shit.
-谁在那里？ -朱里奥？
- Who is that? - Julio?
-你在哪里？ -朱里奥？朱里奥？
- Where are you? - Julio? Julio?
你们听到了吗？可恶
Did you hear it? Damn.
-你在哪里？ -朱里奥？
- Where are you? - Julio?
-你是谁？ -谁？
Who are you? “Who?
朱里奥？你是朱里奥？
Julio? Julio?
-你能听见我说话？ -你们听不见他说话吗？
- You can hear me? - Don't you hear him?
太难以置信了
I don't believe this.
嘿 你听我讲 我的名字叫森姆维特
Hey, you! Hey, you! My name is Sam wheat.
你能听见我说话吗？森姆维特 讲我个名
Listen, can you hear me? Sam wheat. Say my name. Say it.
别缠着我 快收声 讲我个名 快讲  森姆维特
- Leave me alone! Stop it! - Say my name. Say it! Sam wheat.
讲我个名 森姆维特 快讲 说话呀 奥德梅 快讲句说话
Say my name. Sam wheat. Say it. Talk to me, oda Mae. Say something.
森姆维特！
Sam wheat!
天啊
Jesus.
森姆维特？ 森姆维特？
- Sam wheat? - Sam wheat?
我发誓不再骗人了 我保证 要我怎么做都可以
I swear, no more cheating. I promise. I'll do anything. I'll do penance.
让我受苦赎罪吧 但是请让那家伙消失
Give me penance, but make that guy go away.
不可能
No way.
无事啦
It's okay.
真的无事啦
好了 大师
All right, sister.
-我简直不能… -你不会有事的
- I can't... - Yeah, you're all right.
我妈妈能通灵 我祖母也能
My mother had it. And my mother's mother had it.
她们天生就有这种法力
They... they both had the gift.
她们总是说我也有这种法力 但是我从来就没有 从未有过
And they always said I had it, but I never did. I never had it.
她们给我讲过通灵的情形 她们把一切都告诉了我
They told me what it was like. They told me all about it.
可是现在我有了这种法力 我却不想要它
But now that I got it, I... I don't think I want it.
所以 拜托你快走吧 去找别人吧
So, do me a favor, just go away. Find somebody else.
找别人？ 你真是疯了
Somebody else? You're out of your mind.
是的 我快要被你逼疯了
Yeah, I'm getting there fast.
嗯 我看她的头撞得不轻 比我们想像的更严重
Well, I think she hit her head harder than we think.
嗯 可是她撞到头之前 就开始对着空气自言自语了
Well, she was talking to nobody that wasn't there before she even hit her head.
我看她现在还在说呢 你知道吗 大师有时会这样的
Well, I know she is. But you know, sister can do that.
-你到底在哪里？ -我就站在你旁边
- Where exactly are you? - I'm standing right beside you.
-哦 你就站在我旁边？ -嗯 亲爱的 我们在这里呢
- Oh, you're standing right beside me? - Well, honey, we're right here.
-你是白人吗？ -什么？
- Are you white? - “What?
-白人？-你是白人 对吧？
- White? - You're white, aren't you?
-哦 天啊 你知道我怎么想吗？ -知道 我马上就打电话给医生
- Oh, god, you know what I think? - Yes, I'm gonna call the doctor right now.
我就知道你是白人 为什么找我？
I knew it. It's a white guy. Why me?
听着 你一定要帮我 有一个女人
Listen, damn it. You are going to help me. There's a woman.
她叫莫莉简森 她现在的处境十分危险
Her name is Molly Jensen, and she's in terrible danger.
杀我的凶手潜入了我们的公寓 而且他还会再去的
The man who killed me broke into our apartment and he's gonna go back.
所以你要去警告她
So you've gotta warn her.
你凭什么觉得她会听我的？
Just what makes you think she's gonna listen to me?
你打个电话就得
It's just a phone call.
你听我说…
Look,
…只有你可以帮我
you're all I've got.
你不帮我 我就不走
Now, I'm not leaving until you help me.
我不在乎要花多长时间 因为我可以一直不停地说
I don't care how long it takes, 'cause I can talk forever.
她正在房间里跟白人说话呢
She's talking to white people in the room.
-喂？ -你好
- Hello? - Hi.
-请问你是莫莉简森吗？ -是的
- Is this Molly Jensen? - Yes.
嗯 我叫奥德梅布朗 我是一位灵媒
Well, my name is oda Mae brown. I'm a spiritual reader and advisor,
你的一位朋友 让我带个口信给你
and a friend of yours gave me a message for you.
我知道这听起来有点离谱
Now, I know this is gonna sound a little crazy,
但确实是真的 你要相信我 不要害怕
but it's not, and you gotta believe me. Just don't be afraid.
你是谁？
Who is this?
森姆让我带个口信给你
I got a message from Sam.
-什么？ -森姆维特 他让我打电话给你
- What? - Sam wheat. He asked me to call.
-我早跟你说过会这样的 -你要去找她
- I told you. - You gotta go there.
别妄想了 随便你要怎样 我哪里都不去
Forget it. I'm not going anywhere. I don't care what you do.
（酒铺）
第二段同第一段
Second verse same as the first
我是亨利八世
I'm Henry viii, I am
亨利八世就是我
Henry viii, I am, I am
我娶了隔壁的寡妇
I got married to the widow next door
她之前结过七次婚
she's been married seven times before
每个丈夫都叫亨利 亨利！
and every one was an Henry Henry!
她不嫁威利或森姆 不嫁森姆
She wouldn't have a Willie or a Sam
no, sir!
我是她第八任丈夫 我的名字叫亨利
I'm her eighth old man, I'm Henry
亨利八世就是我
Henry viii, I am, I am
Henry viii, I am
第二段同第一段
second verse same as the first
我是亨利八世
I'm Henry viii, I am
亨利八世就是我
Henry viii, I am, I am
我与隔壁的寡妇结了婚
I got married to the widow next door
行了 行了 行了！ 别唱了！
all right, all right, all right! Stop singing!
你让我去哪我就去哪！ 你别再唱了！
I'll go anywhere you want to! Just don't sing anymore!
我简直不敢相信
I can't believe this.
我来这里干什么？
I can't believe I'm doing this. What am I doing down here?
我从不来市中心的 我讨厌市中心
I never come downtown. I hate downtown.
她可能根本不在家
She's probably not even there.
你在哪？
Where are you?
你让我找哪幢楼？
Which building is it?
-按哪个？ -按3
- Which one? - Push three.
-看到了吧？没人在家 -她在家的 等着 等一下
- See? Nobody's there. - She's there. Just wait. Just wait.
不行 我来这里了 我答应的我都做到了
Look, no. I came down here, I did everything I said I was gonna do.
我也按门铃了 她不在家 我走了 再见
I pressed the button. She's not there. I'm gone. Goodbye.
-就等一下 -对不起
- Just wait one minute. - I'm sorry.
墙上挂着99瓶啤酒 99瓶啤酒
Ninety-nine bottles of beer on the wall ninety-nine bottles of beer
拿下一瓶传给别人
take one down and pass it around
好了 别唱了 好了 好了 我认输了
all right, don't sing! All right, all right, all right!
-喂？ -你好
- Hello? - Yes, hi.
-她听不到你说话 -你好 我是奥德梅
She can't hear you. Hi, I'm oda Mae.
你记得吧昨晚我打过电话 讲关于你的朋友森姆维特的事
You know, I called you last night about your friend Sam wheat.
我早就跟你说了会这样
I told you.
嘿 莫莉！
Hey, Molly!
莫莉简森 我知道你在楼上！ 我知道你能听见我就在这里
Molly Jensen, I know you're up there! I know you hear me! I'm down here!
森姆想跟你说话 这是真的！
Sam wants to talk to you! This is for reall
嘿 你还记得 蒙特哥湾的海星吗？
hey, you remember the starfish in montego bay?
如果他不在这 我怎么会知道这个？
How would I know that if he wasn't here?
嘿 莫莉 我知道你在 绿色内衣上写了自己的名字
Hey, Molly! I know about the green underwear that you wrote your name on!
告诉你吧 这件事要是我也忘不了
I'd never get over that, I'll tell you that.
我知道在里诺市拍的照片 嘿 莫莉
I know about the picture in Reno. Hey, Molly!
问她那件她织的毛衣 在柜子里 织的太大了
Ask her about the sweater she knitted, in the closet, that's too big.
他让我提醒你
He just asked me to remind you of the sweater
柜子里那件你织的毛衣 太大了
that's in the closet that you knitted is too big!
大了四号呢！
Four sizes!
嘿 你听见我说的话了吗？
Hey, you hear me talking to you?
-我听见了 -哦 闭嘴吧 没人跟你说话
- I hear you. - Oh, shut up. Nobody's talking to you.
-你不会用电话吗？ -去你的吧
- Didn't you ever hear of a phone? - Wanna kiss my butt?
-我可不会整天都在这里 -感谢上帝
- I'm not gonna stay down here all day! - Thank god.
嘿 老兄 闭嘴吧
Oh, man, shut up!
莫莉！
Molly!
我数到三就走
I'm gonna count to three, and then I'm out of here.
一二三
One, two, three.
别走 奥德梅 等一下
- No, oda. Wait. - No.
她就是莫莉
It's Molly.
你是莫莉？
Molly?
我是奥德梅布朗
I'm oda Mae brown.
我不认识你 我也不认识这个叫森姆的家伙
I don't know you. I don't know this guy, Sam.
他却害得我好苦
But let me tell you what he did to me.
他唱了一夜《我是亨利八世》 吵得我不能睡觉
He kept me up all night singing I'm Henry viii, I am.
他当初就是唱这首歌 令我跟他约会
That's how he got me to go out with him.
听着 我很对不起 我只是…
Look, I'm sorry.
我只是不相信 这种灵魂不灭的事情
I just don't believe in this life-after-death stuff.
-嗯 告诉她 她错了 -他说你错了
- Well, tell her she's wrong. - He says you're wrong.
-你现在就在跟他说话？ -是的
- You're talking to him right now? - Yeah.
他刚叫我跟你说你错了
He just asked me to tell you that you were wrong.
-那他在哪里？ -我看不到他 只能听见他说话
- So, where is he? - I can't see him. I can only hear him.
我就在这里啊
I'm right here.
你这样说没用 森姆
That doesn't help, Sam.
我正握着她的手
I'm holding her hand.
他说他正握着你的手
He says he's holding your hand.
你这是干什么？
What are you doing?
你为什么这样对我？
What do you think you're doing to me?
如果你觉得 我大老远跑来是我有病
Hey, look, if you think I'd come all the way down here for my health,
那就是你黐线
you're out of your mind.
森姆已经死了 他已经死了
Sam's dead. Okay? He's dead.
-告诉她我爱她 -他说他爱你
- Tell her I love her. - He says he loves you.
森姆从来都不会那样说
Sam would never say that.
[我都系]！跟她说[我都系]
Ditto! Tell her ditto.
什么[我都系]？[我都系]！
What the hell 1s ditto? Ditto!
小姐 老实跟你讲 我都不知道我是怎么做到的
Man, to tell you the truth, I don't know how I'm doing this.
我静静话你知 这种事从来没在我身上发生过
You know, confidentially, nothing like this has ever happened to me before.
我是说我从来都不会通灵 现在可好我想停都停不了
I mean, nothing. And now I can't turn it off.
这个是他吗？这个是你？
Is this him? Is this you?
-是的 -对
- Yeah. - Yeah.
挺帅的 白人 但是挺帅的
Cute. White, but cute.
我不明白的是他为什么要回来
What I don't understand is why did he come back?
-我不知道 -为什么他还在这里？
- I don't know. - Why is he still here?
他卡在两个世界之间了
He's stuck, that's what it is. He's in between worlds.
你知道吗 有时候有这情况 灵魂出窍得太快了
You know, it happens sometimes. The spirit gets yanked out so quick
本体会感觉还有未完的心愿
that the essence still feels like it has work to do here.
-你别再乱讲？ -我才没有乱讲呢
- Would you stop rambling? - I don't think I'm rambling.
我只是在回答她的问题
I'm just answering her question.
-他现在脾气可真差 -我脾气才不差呢
- He's got an attitude now. - I don't have an attitude.
不 你就是脾气差 我正在跟他争论
Yes, you do have an attitude. We're having a little discussion.
如果你脾气不差
If you didn't have an attitude,
你就不会对我大呼小叫了 对不对？
you would not have raised your voice to me, now, would you?
-该死的天 奥德梅 -不许你跟我说该死的天
- God damn it, oda Mae. - Don't you "god damn it" me.
不许你当着我的面 亵渎天父之名
Don't you take the lord's name in vain with me, you understand?
-我可受不了 -你能不能冷静点？
- I don't take that. - Would you relax?
不 你才应该冷静点呢 你已经死了
No, you relax. You're the dead guy.
你要我帮你  就得道歉
You want me to help you? You better apologize.
-那你最好道歉 -老天啊！
- Because I don't take that from anybody. - Jesus Christ!
-到此为止 我要走了 -你在干什么？
- That's it, I'm leaving. - What are you doing?
没人那样跟我说话 你听清楚了没有？
I'm leaving. Nobody talks to me like that. You understand me?
-现在你最好跟我道歉 -对不起 我道歉 可以了吗？
- Now you better apologize. - I'm sorry. I apologize. Okay?
你坐下行不行？请坐
Now would you sit down? Please?
他道歉了
He's apologized.
我需要你把我说的话告诉莫莉
I need you to tell Molly what I'm saying,
你要一字不漏跟她讲 可以吗？
but you have to tell her word for word, all right?
-一字不漏 -可以
- Word for word. - Yes.
他想让我把他的话 一字不漏的告诉你
He wants me to tell you what he's saying word for word.
你现在处境很危险
Molly, you're in danger.
你不能一开口就这么说 你不要走来走去得吗？
Now you can't just blurt it out like that. And quit moving around, will you?
你这样令我头晕 我会用自己的方法告诉她
'Cause you're starting to make me dizzy. I'll just tell her in my own way.
莫莉小姐 你的处境很危险
Molly, you in danger, girl.
-你在说什么？ -我找到杀我的凶手了
- What are you talking about? - I know the man who killed me.
他找到杀他的凶手了
He knows the man who killed him.
凶手的名字叫威利洛佩兹 我还知道他住在哪里
His name is Willie Lopez, and I know where he lives.
凶手是波多黎各人威利洛佩兹 他还知道凶手的住址
His name is Willie Lopez. He's puerto rican. He knows where he lives.
-写下来 -他想让你写下来
- Write it down. - He wants you to write it down.
-你写下来 -我又不是你的秘书
- You write it down. - I ain't no damn secretary.
你就快些写吧
Just do it!
他脾气可真暴躁
He's so testy.
-你想让我写什么 -盛景园303号公寓4D
- What is it you want me to write? - It's 303 prospect place, apartment 4d.
-盛景园303号？ -对
- 303 prospect place? - Yeah.
那是我家附近啊
That's my neighborhood.
莫莉 凶手有我的钱包 有我的钥匙 他来过这里
Molly, he's got my wallet, he's got my key, and he was in here.
凶手有他的钱包和钥匙 之前来过这里
He's got his wallet and his key, and he was in here.
昨天你跟卡尔散步后回来
Yesterday when you came back from your walk with Carl,
你上楼了 跟我们的猫佛洛依德说话
you went up the stairs, you talked to Floyd,
-之后你进屋 脱掉了衣服… -好了 行了
- you went in, took off your clothes... - All right, all right.
昨天你跟卡尔散步回来时 凶手就在这里
When you came in yesterday from your walk with Carl, he was here.
你把衣服脱掉了 凶手什么都看见了
You took your clothes off. He saw everything.
莫莉 你要去报警 这是个阴谋
Molly, you got to go to the police. It was a set-up.
我是被谋杀的
I was murdered.
他说这是个阴谋 让你去报警 他是被谋杀的
He wants you to go to the police. He said it was a set-up. He was murdered.
-恐怕还有其他人也参与了 -听着 还是算了
- There's somebody else involved. - Look, forget it.
我不知道是谁 但是… 关于这件事…
I don't know who, but...
-我不想知道更多了 -等等
- I don't want no more to do with this, okay? - Wait.
-你要去哪？-你什么意思“我要去哪里？”
- Where are you going? - What do you mean, where am I going?
我要走了 我应承诺的事我都做到了
I'm leaving. I did everything I said I was going to do.
不许你再跟着我了 我讲真的 这事到此为止了
And don't be following me, 'cause I'm finished. And I mean it.
祝你在阳世愉快 祝你在阴间愉快 再见
Have a nice life. Have a nice death. Goodbye.
莫莉 这世界上除了你之外 没人比我更愿意相信这是真的
Molly, there's no one on earth besides you who'd want this to be true more than me.
但是你必须理智对待这件事
But you've got to be rational about this.
我是说森姆已经不在这里了
I mean, Sam is no more in this room than...
听我说 我理解你对他的留恋
Look, I understand the need to hang on to him.
我真的理解 但是这件事太荒谬了
I really do. But this is absurd.
我知道这件事看似很荒谬 但这肯定是真的
I know this seems absurd. But it had to be real.
一个在布鲁克林算命的 无缘无故出现在你家门前
How could you believe some fortuneteller from Brooklyn
跟你说了这些 你怎么能就这样相信她呢？
who just shows up at your door?
我坐在那里看着她和他对话
I sat there and watched her have a conversation with him.
我不相信 莫 一点也不相信
I don't buy it, mol. Not for a minute.
那她知道的那些事情呢？
What about the things she knew?
什么事情？
What things?
我们去里诺市旅行时 森姆给我拍的照片
The photo that Sam took of me on our trip to Reno.
卡尔 当时就只有我们两个啊
Carl, we were alone.
还有写了我名字的绿色内衣
And the green underwear that I wrote my name in.
她说森姆知道是谁杀了他
She said Sam knew who killed him.
对
Yeah.
说他是被人设计陷害的
That he was set up.
这事真是越说越离谱了
This is getting deranged.
这简直是胡说八道
We're going off the deep end here.
-她知道名字和地址 -好 莫莉 说得好
- She had a name and an address. - Good, Molly, good.
威利洛佩兹 盛景园303号公寓4D
Willie Lopez. 303 prospect place, apartment 4d.
这真是太离谱了 哦 卡尔
This is sick. Oh, Carl.
真的是太离谱了
This is really sick.
天啊
Oh, god.
莫莉 我不明白 你怎么会相信这种鬼话…
Molly, I don't understand how you could
我是说 这个人可能根本就不存在…
swallow this crap. I mean, this guy may not even exist.
可能这个女人是在利用你 来陷害别人
This woman, maybe she's just trying to use you to set someone up.
你说的对 对极了
You're right. You're absolutely right.
不 不是的 所以我要查清楚这件事
No. That's what I got to find out.
查清楚 什么意思？ 你要怎么查清楚？
What do you mean, find out? How are you gonna do that?
嗯 她说森姆要我去报警
Well, she said Sam wants me to go to the police.
森姆要你去报警？
Sam wants you to go to the police?
天啊 莫莉
Jesus, Molly.
你是不是疯了 你要跟警方说什么？
Are you out of your mind? I mean, what are you gonna tell the police?
你要跟他们说有一个
Are you gonna tell them
开小店的灵媒一直在 跟死去的人对话吗？
that some storefront psychic lady's been communing with the dead?
你知道这样说 别人听了会有什么感觉？
I mean, do you have any idea what that sounds like?
你这等于是说有鬼存在 天啊
You're talking ghosts here, for Christ's sake.
对不起 只是这种事 最让我受不了 你明白吗？
I'm sorry. It's just this stuff just really gets to me, you know.
你不相信我也没关系
It's okay if you don't believe me.
我也想相信啊莫莉
I'm trying to, Molly.
听着
Look,
如果能让你 好过一点的话
if it'll make you feel any better,
我会把这件事查清楚 好吗？
I'll go check this out, okay?
你现在就去休息一下吧
Now, why don't you try and get some sleep?
好吗？可以吗？
Okay? All right?
-我明早给你打电话 -好 晚安
- I'll call you in the morning. - Okay. All right. Good night.
（毒贩子都滚出去！）
要小心啊
Be careful.
卡尔 你来干什么？
Carl. What the hell are you doing here?
你跟谁说了 威利？
Who have you been talking to, Willie?
跟谁说？你这话什么意思？
Talking to? What the hell do you mean?
有个女人知道你的事 你所有的底细
Some woman knows all about you, everything.
她是怎么知道的？
Now where's she getting it from, huh?
我从未对任何人透露过一个字
I haven't said a word to anybody.
妈的 她知道你的名字 也知道你的住址
She knows your name, god damn it. She knows where you live.
很多女人都知道我的住址
A lot of women know where I live.
这不是开玩笑的！
This is not a joke!
她还知道那件谋杀案
She knows about the murder.
无论这该死女人是谁 我希望你把她找出来
Now I want you to find this bitch, whoever she is.
我希望你… 把她除掉知道了吗？
And I want you to just get rid of her, okay?
我那该死的电脑里 还卡着四百万呢
I've got $4 million stuck in a goddamn computer.
如果我找不到那些密码 如果那笔钱不尽快转走…
If I don't get those codes, if that money is not transferred soon,
我就死定了 我们两个都死定了
I'm... dead. We're both dead.
你就不能跟他们说 你只在每月初一洗钱吗？
Why don't you tell them you only launder money on the first of the month?
你他妈的是不是有病？
What the hell is wrong with you?
什么事对你来说都是玩笑吗？
Is everything a joke?
你杀了人
You killed a man.
你是去偷他的钱包的 杀人对你来说也是开玩笑吗？
You were supposed to steal his wallet. Was that a joke?
老兄 我可是帮了你一把啊 还是免费的
Man, I did you a favor, man. That was a freebie.
这些洗钱的人都是毒贩子 知道吗？
Look, these are drug dealers, okay?
这件事你可千万别给我搞砸 威利
Just don't blow this for me, Willie.
我会失去工作 还可能坐牢
I'd lose my job. I could go to jail.
那笔钱里有八万可是我自己的
$80,000 of that money is mine.
就把森姆公寓的钥匙给我吧
Look, just let me have the key to Sam's apartment.
我自己去拿电话簿可以吗？
I'll get the address book myself, okay?
混蛋！你这该死的混蛋！
Bastard! You goddamn bastard!
为什么？为什么？ 我还当你是朋友
Why? Why? You were my friend!
我本来活着的 你这该死的 我本来活得好好的
I had a life, god damn you. I had a life!
本来我自己也不相信这种事
Look, I don't even believe in this stuff myself.
但她说的是真的
But she was real.
你觉得如果她说的不是真的 我还会来这里吗？
What? You think I'd come down here if it wasn't real?
是你跟我说如果有新的线索 就应该来的
You know, you told me if I had any new information that I should come.
所以我来了
So here I am.
我知道这件事听起来很可笑
I know how this sounds.
我自己都快听不下去了
I mean, I hear myself saying it and I want to cringe.
但是这个女人知道一些 她本不可能知道的事情
But this woman knew things she couldn't have known.
森姆只跟我说过的事情
Things Sam only said to me.
好吧 据这位灵媒所说
Okay, according to this psychic lady,
到处都有鬼魂和幽灵
there are ghosts and spirits all over the place,
一直在看着我们？
watching us all the time, huh?
该死 那我以后再不敢除衣服了
Well, hell, I'm never gonna get undressed again.
失陪了 我还有更重要的事要做
Excuse me. I've got more important things to do.
那人的名字叫威利洛佩兹
The guy's name is Willie Lopez.
我只是请你们查一下
All I'm asking you to do is check it out.
好吧
Okay.
你就在这里等着吧 我去看下 这个人有没有案底 可以吗？
You just wait here and let me see if the guy's got a record, all right?
很好
Great.
（纽约警署）
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
威利洛佩兹的档案在哪
Where's the file on Willie Lopez?
没有威利洛佩兹的档案
There's no file for a Willie Lopez.
他可能是她想要报复的前度男友
He was probably some old boyfriend she was trying to get even with.
这位灵媒师的案底 倒是历史悠久啊
Now, this psychic woman's got a record that goes back a long way.
1967年在什里夫波特
1967, shreveport,
因伪造文书和贩卖假身份证
forgery, selling false ID.
被判服刑一年
Served one year in 1971.
1971年在巴吞鲁日 因诈骗罪被捕
Baton Rouge, arrested for fraud.
涉嫌多项诈骗案 服刑10个月1974年…
Numbers racketeering, served 10 months, 1974, and...
这不可能
Look, this is impossible.
她简直犯案累累啊
It goes on and on.
她知道一些很隐私的事
She knew things. Private things.
她怎么可能知道这些事？
Now, how could she have known all that?
他们通常会看讣告
A lot of times they read the obits.
她只需要找到「银行家」 这个词就行了
All she had to do was see the word "banker." Boom.
她们甚至会翻你的垃圾桶 去找有用的资讯
Hell, they even go through your garbage to find things they can use.
信件 旧文件 花不多功夫
Letters, old papers, it doesn't take much.
不是的
No.
她所讲的都是真的
It was real.
她知道我织过的一件毛衣
She knew about a sweater I knitted.
知道我们一起唱过的歌
And songs we sang.
我们蒙特哥湾的旅行
Our trip to montego bay.
对不起 我知道这很难接受
I'm sorry. I know this is hard.
人们愿意相信这样的事
People want so much to believe.
因为他们很悲痛 很脆弱
They're grieving. They're vulnerable,
愿意不惜一切来换取 哪怕是最后的一刻
and they will give anything for one last moment.
相信我 这些人非常精于此道
Believe me, these people know what they're doing.
我理解你现在的感受 但是你是可以起诉她的
And I know how you must feel, but you know you can press charges.
不用了
No.
谢谢
Thank you.
（输入密码：）
上帝保佑这个密码对吧
Oh, god, let this be it.
（输入密码：XXX-XXX）
（无效） （有效）
太好了
Yes.
喂 你好
Hello?
-是艾迪吗？ -我是卡尔布鲁纳 什么事？
- Eddie? - Yeah. It's Carl bruner. What's up?
我很好 一切都很顺利 准备就绪了
I'm fine. Yeah, everything's fine. Just, we're all set.
-很好 -告诉我你需要我做什么
- Good. - Just let me know what you want me to do.
好 我需要你把那12个 独立帐户中的钱
Okay, I want you to transfer the money from the 12 separate accounts
都转入丽塔米勒 名下的一个户口
into a single account under the name Rita Miller.
好的
Okay.
明天交易关闭前五分钟 也就是下午三点五十五分
Tomorrow at five minutes before closing, 3:55 P.M.,
把所有的钱转入 纳索第一岛银行
transfer the full account to the first island bank of Nassau,
登录号是4869580
registry number 4869580.
-办完后给我们打个电话 -好的 没有问题
- Call us when it's done. - Okay, I've got it.
请转告包斯德先生 不会再有任何问题了 好吗？
Just tell Mr. balistreri that there won't be any more problems, okay?
-好 我会帮你转告的 -谢谢
- Yeah, I'll do that. - Thank you.
做得好卡尔
Good work, Carl.
（用户名：米勒瑞塔）
（联合现金账户：400万）
莫莉 为什么你听不见我说话？
Molly, why can't you hear me?
我需要你
I need you.
-谁啊？ -我是卡尔 莫莉
- Who is it? - It's Carl, Molly.
不 别开门 莫莉 别开 他是谋杀我的人
No. Don't open it, Molly. Don't open the goddamn door. He's a murderer.
-你好 -你好
- Hi. - Hey.
听着 对不起 我知道很晚了 很抱歉来打扰你
Listen, sorry, I know it's late. I'm sorry to disturb you.
我只是… 我一整天都在想着你
I just... I've been thinking about you all day.
对于昨天晚上发生的事 我感到非常抱歉
And I feel really lousy about... About what happened last night.
这些超自然的事真的…
This supernatural thing just really...
听我说 你不必担心这个 真的 没事的
Listen, don't worry about it. Really, it's okay.
不 是我不对 你想向我倾诉 我却没有听
No, it's not. You needed me to hear you and I didn't.
我没有给你支持 这是… 这是不对的
I wasn't there for you, and that was... That was wrong.
只是…我只是…
It's just I... I just...
我想让你知道 我是你的朋友 莫莉
I want you to know that I'm your friend, mol.
-谢谢你 卡尔 -你从来 都不是我们的朋友！
- Thanks, Carl. - You were never our friend.
-你能这么说对我意义重大 -我也一样
- That really means a lot to me. - Me, too.
我买了些日本苹果梨 我知道你喜欢吃
So I brought you some Japanese apple-pears. I know you like them.
-谢谢 你真好 -我可以进去一下吗？
- Thanks. That's very sweet. - Could I come in for a second?
我不会坐太耐的 今天过得不太好
I won't stay long. It's just been one of those days.
-一起喝杯咖啡什么的可以吗？ -好吧
Maybe a cup of coffee or something? Yeah.
-进来吧 -别让他进来 莫莉
- Come on in. - No, Molly.
你看起来有点紧张 你还好吗？
You seem a little tense. Are you okay?
还好 我没事
No, I'm fine.
只是 唉 怎么跟你说呢？ 最近的日子有点难熬
It's just, god, what can I tell you? It's been tough.
我是说..你知道的 我还在为发生的事难过
It's... I mean, you know, it just still hurts so much.
-你这个无耻的骗子 -除此之外
- You lying snake. - And then on top of it,
还有一些工作上的事
it's stuff at work.
他们给了我自己的帐户 这是好事
They've given me my own accounts, which is good.
但是我还没有时间去适应
But I just haven't really had time to adjust,
以及学习所有的东西
kind of absorb everything.
其实也没什么
It's no big deal.
没事的
Yeah.
-可以给我再加点奶油吗？ -当然
- Can I have just a little more cream? - Yeah.
哦 该死 怎么会这样？
Oh, shit. Jesus. I can't believe I did that.
-你没事吧？ -我没事
- Are you all right? - Yeah, I'm fine.
唉 天啊
Oh, god.
-给我吧 我用洗衣机洗洗 -不用了 没事
- Here, let me throw that in the washer. - No, don't worry about it. It's okay.
没事的 只是…
It's just...
-要不我再给你拿件恤衫？ -不用了一会儿就干了
- You want me to get you another shirt? - No, it's fine. It'll dry.
-用不了太久 -给你
- Just take a minute. - Here you go.
今天你去哪了 我还以为你会
So where were you today? I thought you were gonna
来银行签那些档呢
come into the bank and sign those papers.
嗯 我本来是打算去 但是我没有时间
Well, I was supposed to, but I didn't have time.
我去了警察局
I went to the police.
你去了？ 怎么跟他们说的？ 警员说了什么？
You did? Wow, what did you tell them? What did they say?
整件事糟透了
It was awful.
我感觉自己真笨
I felt really stupid.
他们找出了这女人的案底 至少有10英寸厚
They brought out a file on this woman, and... at least 10 inches thick.
惯骗犯？
A rip-off artist, huh?
不是的 莫莉
No, Molly.
你知道吗最可悲的是…
You know, the sad thing
…我竟然相信了她
is that I believed her.
莫莉
Molly,
有时人需要相信一些事情
sometimes we need to believe.
为什么？有什么意义呢？
Why? What's the point?
莫莉 面对生活的现实很难
Molly, it is not easy to face the realities of life.
所以你要原谅自己有时候
Sometimes you've gotta give yourself that.
你只要记住 你们曾经的相爱
What you've got to remember is the love that you guys felt.
我是说 这才是真实的 记住森姆有多好
I mean, that's what's real. You've got to remember how good Sam was,
他有多么爱你
how much he loved you.
你曾经是他的一切 莫莉 你就是他的生命
You were everything to him, Molly. You were his life.
我感觉好孤单
I feel so alone.
你并不孤单知道吗？
You're not alone, okay?
你有自己的工作 你才华横溢
You've got your work. You're incredibly talented. You're young.
年轻还这么漂亮
You're fantastically gorgeous.
我不知道什么才是真的
I don't know what's real anymore.
不知道该想些什么
I don't know what to think.
就想森姆吧
Just think about Sam.
想想你们共度的时光
Think about the time you guys had together,
是多么的美好
how wonderful that was.
是啊
Yeah.
把你的感情释放出来 莫莉 没关系的
Let your feelings out, Molly. It's okay.
人生总是变化无常
Life turns on a dime.
你知道吗？
You know?
人们觉得自己有的是时间
I mean... people think that... they're there forever
总是会有明天 但这都是废话
That there's always gonna be tomorrow, but that's bullshit.
森姆让我们明白了
Sam taught us that.
人活着要把握现在…
You have to live for now,
…把握今天
for today.
-我做不到 对不起 -没事的
- I can't. I'm sorry. - It's okay.
-我不能这样 太快了 -真的没事
- I can't. It's just too soon. - It's okay.
你一直对我很好 卡尔
You've been great, Carl.
-但是我恐怕要请你离开了 -好的 我完全理解
- But I need you to leave. - It's okay. I understand, totally.
请你走吧
Please.
明天晚上我们可以共进晚餐吗？ 只是聊聊天而已
Could we just have dinner tomorrow night? Just talk.
你有兴趣吗？
Can I interest you in that?
-好吧 可以 -太好了
- Yeah, sure. - Great.
嘿
Hey.
-从我的火车上滚下去 -不
- Get off my train. - No.
下去！滚下去！
Get off! Get off!
滚下去！滚下去！滚下去！
Get off! Get off! Get off!
-从这里滚出去！滚！ -不
- Get out of here. Get off. - No.
告诉我你是怎样移动物体的
Show me how you do that.
我要学会那个 如果你不教我我就不走
I want to learn, and I'm not leaving till you teach me.
-滚下去！ -不
- Get off! - No.
滚下去！
Get off!
你这个固执的混蛋
You stubborn asshole.
你在做什么？ 你到底在做什么？
What are you doing? What the hell are you doing?
这么问什么意思我在…
What do you mean, what am I...
你在试着用手指移动它
You're trying to move it with your finger.
你没法用手指移动它 你已经死了
You can't push it with your finger. You're dead.
要移动它全靠你的意念
It's all in your mind.
你的问题在于 你觉得自己还活着
The problem with you is you still think you're real.
你觉得你还穿着那些衣服吗？
You think you're wearing those clothes?
你觉得你正蹲在地上吗？ 可笑！
You think you're crouched on that floor? Bullshit!
你的身体已经不存在了 孩子 现在全靠这里
You ain't got a body no more, son. It's all up here now.
如果你想移动一个东西 你必须靠意念来移动它
If you want to move something, you've got to move it with your mind.
你要集中意念 听到我说什么吗？
You gotta focus. You hear what I'm saying?
怎样？怎样集中意念？
How? How do you focus?
我不知道怎样集中 但你就是要集中意念
I don't know how you focus. You just focus.
-你是怎么做到的？ -你必须将所有的情感
- How did you do that? - You gotta take all your emotions,
你全部的愤怒 全部的爱和恨
all your anger, all your love, all your hate,
都灌注于丹田处
and push it way down here into the pit of your stomach.
然后像原子炉一样爆发
And then let it explode like a reactor.
好 好的
Okay, okay.
别笑了！
Don't laugh!
做得好 小子！
Way to go, kid!
我成功了
I did it.
我成功了 -做得好
- I did it. - Way to go.
从丹田发力 像我告诉你的那样
From your gut, like I told you.
慢慢来 你有的是时间
Give it time. What else have you got?
你在这里留多久了？
How long have you been here?
自从有人把我推下去 就一直在这里
Since they pushed me.
-有人把你推下去的？ -是的 有人把我推下去的
- Someone pushed you? - Yes, someone pushed me.
-谁推的？ -怎么 你不相信我？
- Who? - What, you don't believe me?
你认为我是掉下去的？ 我是自己跳下去的？
You think I fell? You think I jumped?
去死吧 我时辰还未到
Well, fuck you! It wasn't my time.
我本不该死的 我不该在阴间的
I wasn't supposed to go! I'm not supposed to be here!
如果能吸上一口烟 我愿意不惜一切代价
Oh, I'd give anything for a drag.
-哪怕只吸上一口烟！ -你没事吧？
- Just one drag! - Are you all right?
你是谁？ 你为什么缠着我？
Who are you? Why are you hounding me?
谁派你来的？
Who sent you?
离我远点！走开！ 别来烦我！
Leave me alone! Leave me alone! Leave me alone!
（市场安全银行和信托公司 我们让一切变得简单）
太好了
Yes!
（第42街）
…所以你需要集中注意力 如果你专心就能召唤到他
So you need to concentrate, 'cause if you concentrate, you'll probably rouse him.
-他叫什么名字？-奥兰多
- Now what's his name again? - Orlando.
奥兰多
Orlando.
奥兰多 奥兰多 这里有叫奥兰多的吗？
Orlando, Orlando, is there an Orlando here?
-我在这 -他在这
- I'm here. - He's here.
-奥德梅 我… -森姆！
- Oda Mae, I... - Sam!
-我的天啊 -对不起 我是奥兰多
- What the hell? - Excuse me, I'm Orlando.
请那边排队
The line's over there.
奥德梅 这些鬼都是从哪里来的？
Oda Mae, where did all these ghosts come from?
-你也能听到他们说话？ -你还问我能不能听到？
- You can hear them, too? - Hear them? Can I hear them?
我早上就听到 晚上也听到
I hear them in the morning. I hear them in the evening.
冲凉的时候都能听到
They're coming into the shower.
你是不是把我介绍给 你在全世界遇见的鬼了
Sam, what the hell did you do to me? Did you tell every spook in the world you met about me?
-我这甚至有从新泽西来的鬼 -天啊
- I got spooks from Jersey coming in here. - Jesus.
你一定不会相信现在发生的事 连我自己都不相信
There's stuff going on you wouldn't believe. I don't even believe it.
-真神奇 你真的能通灵了 -是的
- It's amazing. You're really doing it. - Yes, I know.
你觉得怎么样？
How do you like that?
-你们两个能快点吗？ -哦 放松一点 冷静
- Can you two please hurry this up? - Oh, chill out. Chill out!
听我说 奥德梅 你要再帮我一次
Listen, I need your help again, oda Mae.
-我们要去办件事 -不
- There's something we need to do. - No.
我什么事也不跟你去办 森姆
I'm not doing anything else with you, Sam.
你还在眷恋 已经不属于你的人世
Look, you're holding onto a life that doesn't want you anymore.
你已不属于人世了 别再做游魂野鬼了
It doesn't want you. Give up the ghost.
-你是跟我说话吗？ -我看起来像是在跟你说话吗？
- Are you speaking to me? - Does it look like I'm speaking to you?
我跟你说话的时候你会知道的 你应该集中精力
You'll know when I'm talking to you. You supposed to be concentrating, aren't you?
请你试着集中精力行不行？ 非常感谢
Now, you want to try it? Thank you very much.
森姆 你还不走吗？ 我还有事要做呢
Now, Sam, are you gonna get out of here? 'Cause I got work to do.
好 那你就留在那里
Fine, then stay there.
嘿 打扰一下 你准备好了吗？
Excuse me. Excuse me. You ready now?
我们开始吧
Let's do it.
奥德梅 我现在就要跟你讲 我有个计划
Oda Mae, listen. I got to talk to you now. I've got a plan.
你看 我都想清楚了
You see, I figured this thing out.
我们是有办法的 我们只要…
There's something we can do. All we gotto do is...
奥德梅？
Oda Mae?
欧蒂沙？
Ortisha?
奥兰多？是你吗？
Orlando? Is that you?
欧蒂沙 你在哪里？
Ortisha, where are you at? I can't hardly see.
-这里 她在这里 -在你面前 我就在这里
- Here. She's here. - In front of you. I'm right here.
天啊 亲爱的 你的头发怎么了？
Damn, baby! What'd you do to your hair?
奥兰多 你喜欢吗？ 这发式叫「秋天的日出」
Orlando, you like it? It's Autumn sunrise.
滚出我的身体 你这混蛋！
Get out of me, you son of a bitch!
以后不许你再这么做 奥兰多！
Don't you ever do that to me again. Orlando!
-我几乎动不了 -你早该知道的
- I can barely move. - Now, you should know better than that.
-附到人体上会使你筋疲力尽 -全都给我出去！
Jumping into bodies wipes you out. Everybody out!
奥兰多怎么了？保险单在哪？
What happened to Orlando? Where's the insurance policy?
你聋吗？ 我说了全都给我出去！
Are you deaf? I said everybody out!
全都出去 出去 出去 出去！
Everybody out! Get out, get out, get out!
全都给我出去！
Everybody get out!
出去！
Get out!
-你就是那个算命的？ -你是谁？
- You the fortuneteller? - Who are you?
问得好
That's an interesting question.
还是你来告诉我吧
Why don't you tell me?
-威利 -威利？
- Willie. - Willie?
-盛景园的威利？ -快跑！快！
- Prospect place Willie? - Get out of here! Fast!
大师！大师！ 奥德梅
- Sister! Sister! - Oda Mae!
我没事 我没事
I'm all right. I'm all right.
奥德梅 我们有麻烦了 你一定要帮我
Oda Mae, we're in trouble, so you've got to help me.
什么我们？谁是我们？
What do you mean we? Who's we?
你已经死了 你难道不明白？
You're already dead. Don't you understand?
这些人想要杀我
These people are trying to kill me.
你说对了他们还会回来的
Yeah, you're right. And they'll be back.
你就不能找个房子躲着吗？
Look, why don't you just find a house to haunt, you know?
找些链子再搞一些 哗啦啦的声音
Get some chains and rattle them or something.
我有个计划一定会成功的
Will you listen to me? I have a plan and it will work.
但是你要用你的假证件
But you've gotta get some of your fake ids.
休想
Forget it.
如果你按照我说的做 他们以后再也不会来烦你 我保证
If you do this, they'll never bother you again, I promise.
以童子军的名誉担保
Scouts' honor.
好吧
All right.
我该怎么做？ 你到底要我做什么？
What do I have to do? What exactly do I have to do?
你有好看的衣服吗？
You got a nice dress?
我不觉得我穿的衣服 有什么问题
I don't see what's wrong with what I'm wearing.
对不起 我只是开个玩笑 我喜欢你的鞋
I'm sorry I made a joke. I love your shoes.
我看你不喜欢 我还是回家吧
No, I don't think you do. You know, I think I'm gonna go home.
我要回家了
I'm going home
因为我对银行业务一窍不通 我觉得这样行不通的
because I don't know anything about banking. I don't know that this is gonna work.
你放松一些吗？
Oda Mae, would you just relax?
（请捐款）
Please donate.
我好紧张
Listen, I'm nervous.
我知道你很紧张
I know you're nervous,
但是我会帮你渡过这关的
but I will get you through it.
-假驾驶执照做的非常好 -森姆  我看我办不到这事
- And the fake driver's license is great. - Oh, Sam, I don't think I can do this.
你可以的 往正前方走 楼梯上方写着「新帐户」的地方
You can do it. Straight ahead of you. A stairway that says, "new accounts."
-我们就去那里 -我才不给他们钱呢
- That's where we're going. - I'm not giving them no money.
-照我说的做 不要说话 -好
- Just do what I say and don't talk. - Okay.
-告诉她来为新帐户填签名卡 -我能为你效劳么？
- Tell her you're here to fill out a signature card for a new account. - Can I help you?
是的 我来为新帐户填签名卡
Yes, I'm here to fill out a signature card for a new account.
您知道帐号是多少吗？
And do you know your account number?
92631043
92631043.
-926… -31043
- 926... - 31043.
…31043
31043.
-丽塔米勒 -谁？
- Rita Miller. - “Who?
-什么？ -告诉她丽塔米勒
- What? - Tell her Rita Miller.
丽塔米勒 在你开户的时候
Rita Miller. Didn't they have you sign a card
他们没让你填签名卡吗？
when you opened the account?
告诉她卡尔布鲁纳 通过电话帮你开户
Tell her Carl bruner opened it for you by phone
叫你今天来签名的
and asked you to come in today.
是这样的 卡尔布鲁纳 通过电话替我开户
You see, Carl bruner, he opened it for me by phone,
他告诉我今天来签名
that account, and now he's asked me to come in today.
我明白了
I see.
-这样对吗？ -对
- Is that right? - Yeah.
好了 请在底部的线上签名
All right. Just sign this card on the bottom line, please.
我可以用一下你的笔吗？ 非常感谢
May I use your pen? Thank you so much.
不 不对 不对！丽塔米勒
No, no, no! Rita Miller.
很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我需要一张新表格 我签错了名字
You know, I... I need another one. I signed the wrong name.
告诉她确保你的表格 直接存入三楼的文档
Now, tell her to make sure it goes straight up to the third floor file,
因为你有一笔交易要做
because you have a transaction to make.
请确保这张表格直接转到三楼 因为我要去注入一些
Please make sure this goes right up to the third floor file, because I have a transfusion to make.
-什么？ -我们走吧
- A what? - Let's go.
你明白我的意思 我可以留着这支笔吗？
You know what I mean. Can I keep this pen?
-当然 可以 -非常感谢
- Yes, sure. - Thank you so much.
再见
Bye-bye.
-我就喜欢这些笔 -你竟问「我可以留着这支笔吗？」
- I just love these pens. - Then keep the pen.
-你什么总让我…？ -你要这支笔做什么？
- Why are you always making me... - What do you want to keep the pen for?
-我是卡尔布鲁纳 -你好 卡尔
- Carl bruner speaking. - Hi, Carl.
-包思德先生 -包思德？
- Mr. balistreri. - Balistreri?
-卡尔 是我 约翰 -约翰 是约翰啊 对不起
- Carl, it's me, John. - John, John. Sorry.
有…有什么事吗？
What... what... what's up?
我有布兰得利 投资组合的内幕消息
I've got the info on the Bradley portfolio.
哦 好的 很好 我迟点打电话给你 好吗？
Oh, right, okay, look, I'll just... I'll pick it up later. All right?
-好的 我6点前都在 -好
- All right. I'll be here till 6:00. - Good.
就是这里 估计我怎么劝 这帽子你也是要戴着
This is it. I don't suppose I can talk you into losing the hat.
你要是一直烦我 就自己在这里办这事吧
You keep messing with me, you'll be here by yourself.
告诉保安你要见赖尔弗格森
Tell the guard you're here to see Lyle Ferguson.
赖尔弗格森
Lyle Ferguson.
你好 我来见赖尔弗格森
Hi. I'm here to see Lyle Ferguson, please.
-你预约了吗？ -没有 我为我的健康而来
- Do you have an appointment? - No, I'm here for my health.
告诉他瑞泰米勒来了
Don't say that. Tell him Rita Miller's here.
你就告诉他丽塔米勒来了 请稍等
You just tell him Rita Miller's here. Just one moment, please.
说话不要加盐加醋
Don't embellish.
请问你说什么？
Excuse me?
听我说 这个赖尔弗格森是个混蛋
Now, listen. This guy Ferguson's a real jerk.
我认识他五年了 他还以为我叫…
I've known him for five years, and he still thinks my name's...
-你为什么要小声说话？ -安静一点听我讲
- Why are you whispering? - Just be quiet and listen.
他是一个社交白痴 所以你什么都不用担心
He's a social moron, so you don't have anything to worry about.
告诉那保安 赖尔弗格森认识你
Just tell the guard Ferguson knows you.
你去年在布鲁斯特圣诞聚会上
You spent time with him and his wife, Shirley,
与他和他的妻子雪丽结识的 记住了吗？
at the Brewster's Christmas party last year. Got it?
-你有什么事要见他？ -什么？他不记得我了？
What is this in regards to? “What? He doesn't remember me?
去年我们一起参加过 布鲁斯特的圣诞聚会
Oh, we spent all that time at the Brewster's Christmas party last year.
他和他可爱的妻子雪丽都去了 那里可真美啊
He and his lovely wife, Shirley. It was beautiful.
很大的圣诞树 到处都是成千上万的礼物
A big old tree and thousands of presents everywhere. It...
放屁了
Gas.
我有时会放屁 没事的 放屁而已
I get a little gas from time to time. That's all. Gas.
-别戳我！ -不要过份浮夸
- Quit poking me! - Well, don't overdo it.
这就容易了 弗格森在那次聚会上喝的烂醉
Now, listen, this'll be easy. Ferguson was so drunk at that party,
就算跟天娜特纳说过话 他都不会记得
he could've had a conversation with Tina Turner and he wouldn't remember.
-我可不确定 森姆 -我们过去吧
- I don't know, Sam. - Here we go.
你好 你好
Hello. Hello. Yes.
当然 好 好久不见了
Of course, yes. Well, it's been a long time.
是啊 好久不见了 问他鲍比和斯努奇怎么样了
Oh, a long time. Ask how Bobby and snooky are doing.
顺便问一下 鲍比和斯努奇还好吗？
By the way, how are Bobby and snooky doing?
好 很好 谢谢 谢谢关心
Fine. Fine. Thank you. Thank you for asking.
你家里人都怎么样？
And how is your family?
-他们很好 -好极了
- Oh, couldn't be better. - Well, wonderful.
告诉他你想知道他们的 直布罗陀证券情况怎么样？
Tell him you've been wondering how they did on the Gibraltar securities.
我想知道你们的 直布罗陀证券情况怎么样
I was just wondering, how did you do on the Gibraltar securities?
直布罗陀证券？
The Gibraltar securities?
这个证券我们获得最高盈利了
Well, it looks like we topped out on that one, huh?
-肯定的 -肯定的
- We sure did. - We sure did.
-那条资讯非常有用 -都是老兰迪的功劳
- That was a very useful tip. - Good old Randy.
-多得了老兰迪啊 -是啊
- Good old Randy. - Right.
他的脑袋够聪明
Got a good old head on his shoulders.
-是[她]的脑袋 -哦[她]的脑袋
- Her shoulders. - Her shoulders.
-她的脑袋 -兰迪
- Her shoulders. - Randy.
今天是什么风把你吹来了？
Yeah. So, what... What brings you here today?
-你要关闭帐户 -我要关闭帐户
- You're closing an account. - I'm closing an account.
好的 你知道帐号是多少吗？
Well, wonderful. Do you have your account number?
-有吗？ -有
- Yes”? - Yes.
有 92631043
Yes. 02631043.
92631043
092631043.
-对吗？ -对
- Is that right? - Yeah. - Good.
（联合现金账户：四百万）
丽塔看来今天你要
Well, Rita, it looks like you'll be withdrawing
从我们这里提款四百万了
$4 million from us today.
-四百万？ -说对 快说对！
- $4 million? - Say yes. Say yes!
-对吗？ -对
- Is that correct? - Yes.
是的 对 是的
Yes. Yeah. Yeah. Yes.
-没错 -冷静点 冷静
- That's correct. Yes. - Easy, easy.
好
Yes.
你想怎么提取？
Well, how would you like that?
-要十元和二十元的钞票 -什么？
- Tens and twenties. - Pardon?
告诉他你要银行本票
Cashier's check. Tell him a cashier's check.
-我觉得还是银行本票更好 -银行本票 好的
- I think better, a cashier's check. - A cashier's check. Fine.
当然 你也知道 我们要求每个人都得提供证件
Well, of course, you know, we require identification from everyone.
-例行公事而已 -哦 证件 我…
- It's just procedural. - Oh, ID! Yes. You know, I...
谢谢 我马上就回来
Thank you. Well, I'll be right back.
四百万！
$4 million!
帮我接那索第一岛银行 资料在旋转式名片架
Yeah, get me the first island bank of Nassau. It's on the rolodex.
我们有些档 需要你在这里签一下
Well, we have some things for you to sign here.
这样帐户就正式关闭了
This officially closes the account.
给你笔
And here you are.
签丽塔米勒
Now, sign Rita Miller.
丽塔米勒 我的名字
Rita Miller. That's my name.
我的名字是丽塔米勒 我的名字
My name. Rita Miller. My name.
这是我的名字
My name.
-莫莉 见到你真好 -你好
- Molly, hi. It's good to see you. - Hi.
-奥德梅 我马上就回来 -请你把余下的文件也签了
- Oda Mae, I'll be right back. - A few more if you would, please.
-签哪里都可以吗？ -签这里
- Just anywhere? - Right here.
好
Fine.
银行本票
The check.
你拿好
This... here you are.
你要见的人在最入面
The person you need to see is right down at the end.
好的 谢谢
Okay, thanks.
我老妈把油井赚的钱
Mama took the money that she made in the oil Wells,
都投入到加油泵中
and she sunk it into gas pumps.
你知道吧 就是加油站里的那种
You know, how they have at the gas station?
一般每个加油站里 都有五六个加油泵
And those gas stations have five or six of those things,
所以投资这个非常非常赚钱
so it's very, very lucrative.
-奥德梅 -钱越赚越多
- Oda Mae. - It really adds up.
-奥德梅 我们要走了 说再见 -嗯 我要走了
- Oda Mae, we've gotta go. Say goodbye. - Well, gotta go now.
跟你做生意真的很愉快 非常愉快
It's been a pleasure doing business with you, a real pleasure.
我可以留着这支笔吗？
Now, may I keep the pen?
替我向鲍比和斯努齐道晚安 再见
Say good night to Bobby and snooky for me. I'll see you. Bye-bye.
你为什么要催我走？
Why are you rushing me?
出了什么事？
What is wrong?
-打扰一下 你是赖尔吗？ -哦 你是…
- Excuse me. Lyle? - Oh, yes...
-我是莫莉简森 -莫莉
- Molly Jensen. - Molly.
刚才找你办事的那个女人
The woman you were just doing business with.
-怎么了？ -她想要做什么？
- Yeah? - What did she want?
我是说她的事情 跟我或者森姆有关吗？
I mean, did it have anything to do with me or with Sam?
森姆？为什么这么问？ 没 与你们没关的
Sam? Why, no. No.
-那位是奥德梅布朗 对吧？ -不 她的名字叫丽塔米勒
- That was oda Mae brown, right? - No, her name was Rita Miller,
她是来关闭帐户的
and she was closing an account.
怎么了？有问题吗？
Why? Is there a problem?
不没问题
No. I guess not.
谢谢你
Thank you.
（输入转移授权密码： XXXXX-X）
（帐户已关闭）
卡尔 有什么问题吗？
Carl, is something wrong?
有人动过电脑吗？
Is somebody playing with the computers?
-什么？ -我的一个帐户关闭了
- What? - One of my accounts is closed.
哪个帐户？怎么了？ 需要我帮你打电话叫人吗？
Which account? What's wrong? You want me to call someone?
不用了 没事 我自己解决吧 我来处理
No, it's okay. I can do it. I got it.
四百万 哦 老天啊 这么多钱让我怎么花？
$4 million! Oh, my god, what am I gonna do with this money?
你知道吗 我要买幢楼
L... you know, I'm gonna buy the building.
不 不 我要买个街区 我要把我的妹妹送到减肥中心
No, no, wait. I'm gonna buy the block. I'm gonna make my sister go to a fat farm,
因为 你知道 她太重了
because, you know, she's way too big.
等下 你要干什么… 然后我要…我要买幢楼
Whoa, wait! What are you gonna do... Then I'm gonna... Yeah, I'm gonna buy the building.
等等 奥德梅 我有个主意
Wait, wait, wait, oda Mae, I've got an idea.
-把支票从你的钱包里拿出来 -嗯 你说的对 没错
- Take the check out of your purse. - Oh, you're right. You're right.
我应该把它拿出来 放在没人能偷走的地方
I should take it out. I should put it where nobody can get it.
不 不是 在支票上签名
No, no, no. Endorse it.
不 如果我签了 然后弄丢了 别人就把钱取走了 不 我就…
No, if I endorse it, then if I drop it, somebody will get it. No, I'll just...
这不是你的钱 我从没说过你可以留着这笔钱
It's not your money. I never said you were gonna get the money.
这是一笔不义之财 我就是因为这笔钱被杀的
This is blood money. I was killed for this money.
-你在支票上签名吧 -我知道 可是…
- Now, endorse the check. - I know, but...
森姆 这笔钱你要怎么用？
Well, Sam, what are you gonna do with it?
往那边看 你的左边
Look over there, to your left.
你不会是要我 把这四百万给一班修女吧？
I know you don't think I'm giving this $4 million to a bunch of nuns!
如果你不这样做 他们会找到你的
Oda Mae, if you don't do it, they will track you down.
你只有放弃这笔钱才能自保
Your only protection is to get rid of it.
哦 森姆 别这样 你折磨死我了！四百万啊！
Oh, Sam, come on. You're killing me! It's $4 million!
你就这样想吧 你会上天堂的
Just think of it this way, you'll go to heaven.
我不想上天堂！ 我就想去银行
I don't want to go to heaven! I want to go to a bank
把这该死的支票给兑现了！
and cash the goddamn check!
-你好 -嗯
- Hello. - Yeah.
-日后你会感激我的 -你好吗？
- You'll thank me later. - How are you doing?
-签上丽塔米勒 -我知道
- Now, endorse it Rita Miller. - I know.
捐给圣乔瑟夫庇护所
Make it out to St. Joseph's shelter.
我真不敢相信你竟然要我这样做
I can't believe you're making me do this.
（无家可归者的庇护所）
给她吧
Now, give it to her.
我会给的 会给的 我就想再拿一会儿仅此而已
I will, 1 will. 1 just want to feel it one more time in my fingers, that's all.
-赶紧把支票给修女 -我知道
- Just give the lady the check. - I will!
把支票给她 你做得到的
Hand her the check. You can do it.
-把支票给她 -我会的
- Give her the check. - I will.
上帝保佑你 孩子 上帝保佑你
Bless you, child. Bless you.
给她吧 放手 快放手！
Give it to her. Let go. Let go!
该死
Shit.
我为你骄傲 奥德梅
I'm proud of you, oda Mae.
我才不在乎 你为不为我骄傲呢？
You know something, Sam? I don't care if you're proud of me.
从现在起你离我远点 那个修女要这么多钱做什么？
You stay away from me from now on. What is that nun going to do with it?
她连内衣都不买 什么都不买 我憎恨你离开我远一点
She can't even buy underwear. Nothing. I hate you. Leave me alone.
不要再跟我说话了
Never talk to me again.
我觉得你很棒 奥德梅
I think you're wonderful, oda Mae.
找吧 继续找 你找不到的
Go ahead, search. You'll never find it.
他们会杀了你 卡尔
They're gonna kill you, Carl.
杀了你和威利 你们会变成一堆肥料
You and Willie, you're gonna be fertilizer.
他们会把你们埋在 吉米霍法的旁边
They're gonna bury you right next to Jimmy hoffa.
（谋杀犯）
谁做的？
Who's doing that?
这是谁做的？
（森姆 森姆 森姆…）
-嘿 -嗨
- Hey. - Hi.
我们不是约好吃晚饭嘛
Where were you? I thought we were having dinner.
莫 对不起 出了点麻烦事 我将吃饭的事情都忘记了
I know, mol. I'm sorry. Things got a little crazy. I just forgot.
对 银行那边出了点问题
Yeah, had a little trouble at the bank.
-你忘了？ -对
- You forgot? - Yeah.
你应该早点打电话过来的 我一直在担心你
You know, I wish you would have called me, because I've been really worried.
听我说 莫莉 我有些事情要问你
Listen to me, Molly, I gotta ask you about something.
对 他需要借四百万
Yeah, he needs to borrow $4 million.
上次你说你觉得森姆还在这里 还在跟你说话
When you said that you thought that Sam was here,
当时你是什么感觉？ 他跟你说了什么？
that he was talking to you, what did you feel? What did he say to you?
-这跟你的事情甚什么关系？ -只是…你先听我说
- Why? What does that have to do with anything? - It's just... listen to me for a second.
关于那位灵媒 我想知道她都跟你说什么
This psychic lady, I want to know what she told you.
-我想知道她具体说了什么 -卡尔 放开我 卡尔 停手
- I wanna know exactly what she said. - Carl, let me go. Carl, stop this.
她说什么都无所谓了 又不是真的
It doesn't matter. It wasn't real.
你今晚发生了什么事？
What the hell happened to you tonight?
这是不是与她 白天去银行有关系？
Does this have anything to do with her being at the bank today?
她去银行了？
The bank?
对 弗格森说 她去关闭帐户的
Yeah, Ferguson said she closed an account.
她的名字根本不是奥德梅布朗 是什么丽塔米勒的
Her name isn't even oda Mae brown. It's Rita Miller or something.
卡尔 你没事吧？
Carl, are you all right?
我的胃有点…
It's just my stomach...
天啊
Jesus.
你有没有什么肠胃药之类的？
Do you have any, like, I don't know, some pepto-bismol or something?
-给他山埃差不多 -有 在楼上
- Cyanide. - Yeah. It's upstairs.
你先坐下 我去帮你拿药
Why don't you sit down, and I'll get it?
怎么了？ 小卡尔肚子疼了？
What's wrong? Does little Carl have a little tummy ache?
你要对我做什么？
What are you doing to me?
你现在相信有鬼了？
Now do you believe in ghosts?
我会把这地方点着的 我对上帝发誓
I'll set the place on fire, I swear to god.
-我会把她的喉咙割断 -卡尔
- I'll cut her throat. - Carl.
我对上帝发誓 我会割断她的喉咙
I swear to god. I'll cut her throat.
我需要那笔钱 今天晚上11点前
I need that money, and I want it tonight at 11:00.
如果那个灵媒不把钱带来
If that psychic lady does not bring it here,
莫莉就死定了 听到了吗？
Molly is dead. Okay?
-卡尔 你在跟谁说话？ -没有谁 莫莉 你听我说
- Carl, who are you talking to? - Nothing. Now, Molly, listen to me.
我要出去一下
I have to go, okay?
我现在不能跟你解释 我遇到麻烦了
I can't explain this now, but there is a problem, okay?
-银行那边出了点问题 -卡尔 你吓坏我了
- Something's going on at the bank. - Carl, you're really scaring me.
对不起 我现在没有时间跟你说了
I'm sorry, mol. Look, I don't have time to talk now, but I'll come back about 11:00.
-为什么现在不能说？ -莫莉 我真的没时间
- Why? Why not now? - Molly, I can't talk now.
莫莉 我会回来的 11点 好吗？
Molly, look, I'll come back. What do you say? Like, 11:00, okay?
我对不起这样对你 但这件事真的很重要 我走了
I'm sorry to do this to you, Molly, but it's really important. I gotta go. Okay?
-11点我就回来 -奥德梅
- 11:00. - Oda Mae!
我是阿塞尼奥霍尔 别校你的电视了
I'm arsenio hall. Don't try to adjust your television.
是我长得黑
I'm black.
-我想看「心有灵犀」 -我也爱看「心有灵犀」
- I want to watch love connection. - I love love connection.
-我太喜欢那个男人了 -别转台 这可是阿塞尼奥
- I love that man on there. - Leave that! That's arsenio.
那又怎么样？ 什么怎么样？
S07 - what do you mean, so?
你喜欢「心有灵犀」 你就应该把你的照片寄过去
You love love connection, you ought to send your picture in there.
她已经寄过了 就是他们还没回信
She did already. They just haven't answered yet.
-奥德梅？ -森姆？
- Oda Mae? - Sam?
-怎么又这样了 -我们有麻烦了
- Oh, no. Not again. - Oda Mae, we're in trouble.
他们想要回支票 他们要来找你了
They want the check, and they're coming for you.
所以你得马上从这离开
So you gotta get out of here.
你什么意思 他们想要支票？
What do you mean, they want the check?
那张你说他们 永远不会知道的支票？
The check you said they would never know about?
-奥德梅 发生什么事了 -森姆
- Oda Mae, what's happening? - Sam.
他们来了 他们来了 快点跑 快 跑啊
They're here! They're here! Get out of here! Now! Go!
快点 我们要离开这里！ 出了什么事？
Come on. We gotta go! “What's the matter?
快点 快点
Come on, come on!
敲这家的门
Just knock on the door here.
救命！救命啊！
Help! Help!
-情况紧急 让我们进去 -开什么玩笑？
- It's an emergency. You gotta let us in. - Who are you kidding?
开门啊！
Open up!
你们要做什么？你们不能进来
What are you doing? You can't come in here.
我家的猫不喜欢客人 她会到处尿…
The cat don't like visitors. She'll pee all over that...
他们会找到我们的
They're gonna get us.
森姆在哪？
Where's Sam?
该死！那个死女人刚离开 我去楼下找
- Shit! It looks like the bitch just left. - I'll check downstairs.
卡尔？
Carl?
该死
Shit!
（嘘）
威利！
Willie!
嘿 老兄 你有病吧
Hey, man, you got a serious problem, man.
救救我！救命啊！
Help me! Help!
威利
Willy!
我听见车声 我当时…
I heard the car. I was standing right there.
这家伙已经死了
That dude is dead.
你死了 威利
You're dead, Willie.
不！不要！不要啊！
No! No! No!
救救我！
Help me!
告诉司机快点
Tell the driver to hurry.
嘿 老兄 请你开快点可以吗？
Yo, man, you wanna step on it, please?
太太 我最快就这样了
Listen, lady, I'm driving as fast as I can.
车子有问题了？
Problems?
-卡尔 是你吗？ -不是 是我 奥德梅
- Carl, is that you? - No, it's me, oda Mae.
我知道你是怎么想我的
Listen. Molly, I know what you think of me.
但是你得必须听我说
I know what you think of me, but, look, you gotta talk to me.
你现在处境非常危险 森姆跟我在一起
You are in serious danger. I got Sam here with me.
-我们要进来跟你谈谈 -你给我滚开
- We got to talk. - Get the hell out of here.
-我要报警了 -很好
- I'm calling the police. - Good.
-让她报警 -好 我们正希望你这么做
- Tell her to do it. - Fine. That's what we want you to do.
我们希望你报警
We want you to call the police.
-但是你要让我们进来 -不
- But you've gotta let us in. - No.
你难道不明白吗？
Look, don't you get it?
森姆不是意外被杀的 他是被谋杀的
Sam was not just accidentally killed. He was murdered.
他发现卡尔通过银行洗钱
He found out that Carl was laundering money at the bank.
卡尔这家伙很危险 我告诉你 他刚才还想来杀我
Now, this guy Carl is dangerous. I'm telling you, he tried to kill me.
他还会来杀你
He's gonna try to kill you, too.
你现在非常非常危险
You are in deep, deep trouble.
你为什么这样对我？
Why are you doing this to me?
你为什么要这样对我？
Do you hear me? Why are you doing this to me?
我受不了 我真的… 真的受不了…
I can't. I just... I just can't.
奥德梅 奥德梅 告诉她 她身上穿的这件恤衫
Oda Mae, oda Mae, tell her she's wearing the shirt
曾经被我洒过玛格丽特酒
that I spilled the Margarita on
还有她戴的耳环 是圣诞节我送给她的
and the earrings I gave her for Christmas.
森姆让我告诉你 你现在穿的这件恤衫
Molly, Sam says to tell you you're wearing the shirt
他曾在上面洒过玛格丽特酒 耳环是圣诞节他送给你的
that he spilled the Margarita on and the earrings he gave you for Christmas.
我不是骗子 至少在这件事上我没有呃你
Don't you see? I'm not a fake, not about this.
-给她一分钱 快点 -什么？
- Give me a penny, quick. - “What?
从门底下塞过去一分钱快
Push a penny under the door, now.
在门底下塞过去一分钱？
What you be talking about, push a penny under the door?
照我说的做
Just do it.
告诉她这是好运的象征
Tell her it's for luck.
森姆说这是好运的象征
Sam says it's for luck.
我们在王子街上的 格林街和默瑟街交汇处
We're between Greene and Mercer on prince.
就是邮局对面那幢灰色的大楼
It's the gray building right across from the post office.
谢谢 警官 请快点 我们在这等着
Thanks, sergeant. Please hurry. We'll be waiting.
-没事了 他们马上出发 -太好了
- All right. They're on their way. - Good.
-现在我们做什么 -等着吧
- So, what do we do now? - Just wait.
森姆在这吗？
Is Sam here?
森姆？
Sam?
我就坐在她的旁边
I'm sitting beside her.
他就坐在你的旁边
He's sitting right beside you.
森姆 你能感觉到我吗？
Sam, can you feel me?
我正在用整颗真心去感觉你
With all my heart.
他说他在用整颗真心感觉你
He says with all his heart.
如果能再一次触摸到你 我愿意付出任何代价
I'd give anything if I could just touch you once more.
他说他希望自己还活着 这样就能再次触摸到你
He says he wishes he was alive again, so he could touch you.
我也是
Me, too.
好吧 来吧 你们用我吧
Okay. Okay, look. You can use me.
-用你？ -你们可以借用我的身体
- Use you? - You can use my body.
借用你的身体？
Use your body?
趁我改变主意之前赶快来吧
Just do it quick before I change my mind.
♪ Oh my love
♪ My darling
♪ I've hungered for your touch
♪ A long lonely time
♪ And time goes by
♪ So slowly
♪ And time can do so much
♪ Are you still mine
♪ I
♪ Need your love
♪ God speed your love
♪ To me
♪ Lonely rivers Flow
♪ To the sea
♪ To the open arms
♪ Of the sea
♪ Yeah
♪ Oh my love
♪ My darling
♪ I've hungered
♪ Hungered for your...
莫莉？
Molly?
-莫莉？你在家吗？ -是卡尔
- Molly, are you home? - It's Carl.
-莫莉！ -快走防火梯
- Molly! - Fire escape.
我这是怎么了？
What's happening to me?
莫莉？
Molly?
莫莉！
Molly!
衰人！
Son of a bitch.
快来这边
Come on.
莫莉 看 那边
Molly, look. Look.
哦 我们走吧 从那走
Oh, let's go. Let's go.
莫莉！
Molly!
卡尔 远离我们一点！
Just get away from us, Carl.
-莫莉！ -你是个骗子 骗子！
- Molly! - You're just a liar. Liar!
莫莉 你听我说 这个女人是个窃贼
Molly, you got to listen to me. This woman's a thief.
- 她是个惯骗犯 -为什么？
- She's a con artist. - Why?
-你为什么要这样做？ -不要听她的 莫莉
- Why are you doing this? - Don't listen to her, Molly.
停下！
Stop!
远离我们一点卡尔！
Just get away from us, Carl.
-我已经报警了 -莫莉！
- I've called the police. - Molly!
该死
Shit.
-卡尔 你为什么要这么做？ -你别插手 莫莉 她是个窃贼
- Carl, why are you doing this? - Don't interfere, Molly. She's a thief.
得了 支票给我！ 快把支票给我！
All right, the check. Just give me the check.
-卡尔 收手！ -莫莉！你别管这事
- Carl, no. - Stay out of this, Molly!
衰人！
Son of a bitch!
你别插手这事 莫莉！
Keep out of this, Molly!
你给我下去！
Get off of Mel
在哪里？支票在哪里？ 该死的 支票到底在哪里？
Where is it? Where is it? Where is it, god damn it!
-我给了别人 -你在说谎！
- I gave it away. - You're lying to me.
妈的！不许骗我
Don't lie to me, god damn it!
给我支票！
The check.
我会杀了她 森姆 我对天发誓 我要杀了她
I'll kill her, Sam. I swear to god, I'll kill her.
听着…
Just... look,
森姆你只要将支票给我就可以 好不好？
just give me the check, Sam. Okay?
如果你将支票给我 我跟你保证我会放她走
I promise you I'll let her go if you'll just give it to me.
怎么样？
Okay?
森姆？
Sam?
森姆
Sam.
-哦 卡尔 -怎么回事？
- Oh, Carl. - “What?
不！
No!
你们两个没事吧？
Are you two all right?
森姆？
Sam?
莫莉？
Molly?
我可以听到你说话了
I can hear you.
哦 天啊
Oh, god.
森姆？ 他们在等着你呢 森姆
Sam? They're waiting for you, Sam.
我会想念你的
I'll miss you.
你妈妈一定会以你为荣的
Your mother'd be proud.
我都会想念你的 森姆
I'm gonna miss you, too, Sam.
你也不错
You're all right.
再见 奥德梅
Bye, oda Mae.
再见 森姆
Bye, Sam.
我爱你 莫莉
I love you, Molly.
我一直深爱着你
I've always loved you.
我都系
Ditto.
这感觉很奇妙 莫莉
It's amazing, Molly.
内心深处的爱会至死不渝
The love inside, you take it with you.
再见
See you.
Bye.